let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1. Which is correct with respect to the size of the data types in C?",
    answer: "char < int < float",
    options: [
      "char > int > float",
      "char < int < float",
      "int < char < float",
      "int < chat > float",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2.C Language was developed in which year?",
    answer: "1970",
    options: [
      "1970",
      "1975",
      "1980",
      "1985"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3.Which one of the following is not a reserved keyword for C?",
    answer: "main",
    options: [
      "auto",
      "case",
      "main",
      "default"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4. When we mention the prototype of a function?",
    answer: "​​​Declaring ",
    options: [
      "Defining",
      "​​​Declaring ",
      "Prototyping​​​",
      "Calling",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5.Out of the following snippet, which one will generate random numbers effectively?",
      answer: " rand();",
      options: [
        " rand(time(NULL));",
        " rand(10);",
        " rand();",
        " all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6.  The #include <stdio.h> is a?",
    answer: "Preprocessor directive",
    options: [
      "Inclusion directive",
      "File inclusion directive",
      "Preprocessor directive",
      "None of the above",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "7. Which of the following is an exit controlled loop?",
  answer: "do-while loop.",
  options: [
    "While loop",
    "For loop",
    "do-while loop.",
    "None of the above",
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "8. Which of the following are not standard header files in C?",
  answer: "None of the above",
  options: [
    "stdio.h",
    "stdlib.h",
    "conio.h",
    "None of the above"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. What is the return type of the fopen() function in C?",
  answer: "Pointer to a FILE object",
  options: [
    "Pointer to a FILE object",
    "Pointer to an integer",
    "An integer",
    "A char"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "10. Which of the following is not a storage class specifier in C?",
  answer: "volatile",
  options: [ 
    "volatile",
    "extern",
    "typedef",
    "static"
]
},

];